真相就是 我已经无药可救
The truth is… I'm past saving.
我知道我会有什么样的结局
I know how my story ends.
我也曾是害怕的那个
I've been the one out there scared.
- 迪恩 - 他拼尽全力救你
- And Dean… - He did whatever he could to save you.
这是我欠他的 我欠他一切
I owe him this. I owe him everything.
（走过的路）
- 母亲 - 你会帮我吗
- Mother. - Will you help me?
杀了我儿子
Kill my son.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我要救我哥哥
I'm saving my brother.
别告诉你哥哥我们在做什么
Don't tell your brother what we're doing.
她破解了密码
She's cracked the code.
（匹配）
[咒语]
上帝把黑暗锁了起来
God locked the darkness away.
他创造了一个血印
and he created a mark.
血印既是锁也是钥匙
that would serve as both lock and key,
血印不能解除
The mark cannot be relieved.
否则黑暗会被释放
lest the darkness be set free.
（如今）
这怎么回事
The hell's going on?!
撑住
Hold on!
迪恩
Dean?!
Dean?
没事吧
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
车呢
Where's the car?
在
I-I-it's…
那边一英里处
about a mile that way.
什么
What?
你真不记得了
Seriously?
黑暗来袭 你不见了
The… the darkness hit. You disappeared.
你什么都不记得了吗
You remember none of this?
撑住
Hold on!
她救了我
She saved me.
什么
What?
谁
Who?
黑暗
The darkness.
[邪恶力量 第11季第1集]
（胡安妮塔餐馆）
等等
Wait a second, what…
什么叫 她救了你
What do you mean, she saved you?
你也看到了 黑云来袭时 一片黑暗
You were there. When the storm hit, everything went dark.
但你从车里消失了啊
Yeah, but you just disappeared from the car.
我都不记得这段
I don't even remember that.
我不记得有什么女人把你弄出去了啊
Well, I don't remember some woman pulling you out.
你要我说什么
Well, what do you want me to say, okay?
我本来在车里 然后就突然出来了
I was in the car, and then I wasn't in the car.
我站在地里 她也在
I was in the field, and she was there.
她告诉你她就是黑暗
And she told you she was the darkness.
不 她戴名牌了 你以为呢
No. She was wearing a nametag. What do you think?
她感谢了我
She thanked me.
谢你什么
For what?
释放了她
Setting her free.
那不是你 是我干的
You didn't set her free. I set her free.
无所谓了
It doesn't matter.
是啊 你念的咒
I mean, yeah, you said the spell,
但血印是在我身上 锁和钥匙嘛
but I had the mark, so lock and key.
怎么 她还觉得欠你人情了吗
So, what, now she feels indebted to you or something?
我不知道 她可是黑暗啊
I don't know. She's the darkness.
她有感觉吗
Does she feel anything?
她就只说了谢谢吗
And that's all she said? Thanks?
嗯 她怪怪的
Yeah. She was weird.
她有种气场 一种专注感
But she had this energy about her, this… this focus.
不过话不多
But, yeah, not a talker.
那么我们是屁都不知道
So we know Jack.
我们知道她的样貌
Well, we know what she looks like,
还知道她不是好东西
and we know that she's evil.
问题是 她知道什么
The question is, what does she know?
她从时间之初就被关起来了
I mean, she's been locked away since the beginning of time.
她知道什么是芝士汉堡吗
Does she even know what a cheeseburger is?
我只知道是我们放了她
All I know is that we set her free,
那我们就得把她关回去 不管付出什么代价
and we're gonna put her back in, no matter what it takes.
搞什么
What the…
你也不拦我上车
Just gonna let me get in the car?
看你风风火火的嘛
You were on a roll.
别
Don't!
求你了
Please!
你以为你杀得了我吗
You think you can kill me?
你个该死的
You execrable…
不
No.
他还活着
He's still alive.
别逼我伤害你
Don't make me hurt you.
听到了吗
Do you hear me?
我控制不住 你得赶紧逃
I can't help myself. You have to run.
这里出了什么事
The hell happened here?
有人吗
Hello?
这可不妙
That's not a happy sight.
放松 伙计 别紧张
Hey, easy, buddy. Just stay cool.
先让我们搞清是怎么回事
till we figure out what's going here, okay?
你别逼我哦
Kind of narrowing my options here.
我们不知道他是什么东西
We don't even know what he is.
武器放在地上 慢慢的
Weapons on the ground. Slow.
放松 警官
Easy, officer.
我们是联调局的 我们有警徽
We're FBI, okay? We got badges.
别
Don't.
露出皮肤
Show me some skin.
什么
What?
你俩 快点
Both of you.
你是想看脱衣舞吗
Is this, like, a "Magic Mike" moment?
脖子
Your throats!
你以为我们
Oh, you think we're… we're…
我们都不知道他们怎么回事
We don't even know what these are.
我要知道你们跟他们不一样
I need to know you're not one of 'em.
- 他们是什么 - 快点
- One of what? - Let's go!
好吧 看吧 看到了吧
Okay, all right, look. Huh? See?
很好
Good.
拿证件吧
Let's see those ids.
嗯
Yeah.
好了 你悠着点
All right. Take… take it easy, okay?
坏人干的吗
Bad guys?
钢筋
Rebar.
我想找掩护 摔倒了
I sought cover. I fell.
好吧 跟我们讲讲这里发生了什么吧
Okay. Why don't you tell us what happened here?
911接警 一家人受困
911 reported a family in distress.
我赶到时看到多个行凶者袭击这一家人
I arrived to find several hostiles attacking said family.
天呐 太可怕了
Oh, god, it was horrible.
你干多久了 警官
How long you been on the job, deputy?
三周
Okay, three weeks.
好吧
Okay.
我是迪恩 这是萨姆
I'm Dean. This is Sam.
呼吸 好吗
Just breathe. Okay?
说白话 怎么回事
Speak plain. What happened?
他们把一家人都杀了
They killed them all.
谁
Who?
道路维修工 像一群疯狗一样
Road crew. It was… they were like rabid dogs.
我发了警告枪 但他们不肯停下
I fired off a warning, but they didn't stop.
- 他们 - 你杀了他们所有人
- They… - You killed all these?
我认识其中几个 但他们看起来不…
I knew some of the boys, but they didn't look…
他们不对劲 他们…
Something was wrong. They were…
他们不是人
They're not human.
好了 我可以给你缝一下 但会很疼
Hey, look, I can stitch that up, but, uh, it's gonna be ugly.
这附近有医院吗
You got a hospital around here?
往前走
Up the road.
好吧
All right.
我们走吧
Here we go.
这可好
Well, this is encouraging.
在这儿等着
Wait here.
你怎么想的
So, what are you thinking?
我不知道该怎么想
I don't really know what to think.
我也不知道会怎么样
And I don't know what to expect in here,
所以还是什么都带上吧
so I'm just gonna chuck it all in.
这肯定是黑暗干的 是吧
This is the darkness, right? It's got to be.
怎么 她一来 大家就变疯狂僵尸了吗
So, what, she shows up and everybody goes "28 days later"?
我们就没有啊
We didn't.
但我坐在车里
Yeah, but I was in the car,
你…你说她保护了你
and you were… you said she protected you.
或许不是她
So maybe it wasn't her.
或许是烟的关系 所有暴露在外的人
Maybe it was the smoke, and anybody who was outside,
像道路维修工 就受到了影响
like the road crew, they were exposed.
你也看到了 他们不是人类了
I mean, you saw that. That wasn't human.
怎么 烟把他们变异了吗
So, what? The smoke mutated 'em?
是啊 有何不可
Sure, why not?
几小时前我刚杀了死亡
Just a couple hours ago, I killed death.
我现在什么都能接受了
I'm pretty much open for anything.
但变成什么了
But mutated into what?
好了 一件一件来吧
All right, you know what, one thing at a time.
我们先处理她的伤
Let's just get her some help.
然后再应付后面遇到的
and then we'll deal with whatever comes next.
我得汇报情况
I got to call this in.
不好 再来人 只会死更多
No, bad idea. More people, more bodies.
我们自己应付
We'll deal with this.
这样吧 迪恩 我到处去看看
You know what, Dean, I'm gonna take a look around.
你给她缝针
You sew her up.
好吧 你熟悉这里吗
All right. You know this place?
- 这边走 - 好
- This way. - Okay.
会很疼的
This is gonna hurt like a son of a bitch.
我认识那些人的姐妹 父母
I knew those boys' sisters, their parents.
你不过是履行了职责
You did what you were trained to do.
没事的
It's all right.
没人训练我打死朋友
They don't train you to shoot your friends.
我慌了 我本可以…
I panicked. I could have…
他们已经不是人了
Those boys weren't boys.
他们是怪物了 是威胁
They were monsters, and they were a threat.
任何人都会慌的
Anybody could have panicked.
但不是每个人都能做到你做到的事
Not anybody could have done what you did.
这份工作本该是拯救生命的
This job is supposed to be saving people.
是啊
Yeah, well…
理论上说起来好听多了是吧
It sounds better on paper, doesn't it?
既然你道过谢了
Well, now that you've said your thanks,
我们谈谈接下来会如何吧
let's talk about what happens next.
我喜欢这里
I like it here.
跟你在一起
With you.
我很久没觉得这么平静了
I haven't felt this peaceful in a long, long time.
我们说清楚
Well, let's get something straight…
我不是来给你平静的
I'm not here to bring you peace.
我知道你是什么
I know what you are.
是吗
Really?
我走了那么久 我以为没人记得了
I've been gone so long, I didn't think anyone remembered.
死亡把你说得绘声绘色
Well, death painted a hell of a picture.
我不认识什么死亡
I don't know this death,
他也不了解我
and he doesn't know me.
你是说我不该马上杀了你吗
So, are you saying I shouldn't try and kill you right now?
是我这么说的
Am I saying that?
还是你
Or are you?
有人吗
Hello?
（清洁工）
有人吗
Hello?
他死了吗
Is he dead?
是啊
Yeah, um…
是啊 他死了
Yeah, he's dead.
可以出来了 我是联调局的
It's okay to come out. I'm, uh, FBI.
看看
Here.
我把我的警徽从门下滑进去
I'm gonna slide my badge under the door, okay?
救救我们
Help us, please.
该死
Bollocks.
那就用老办法吧
Old-school it is.
香草薰油
Vanilla spice?
玛恩 我在这儿
Marn? Down here!
怎么回事
What's going on?
你坐好就行
You just sit your tush down, okay?
让我说完
Just let me get this out.
我一直在考虑你说的话
I've been thinking a lot about what you said…
我知道 你说出来时
and… and I know, I lost my chickens.
我发火了
when you put it out there.
但毕竟你妻子跟你说
But it's not every day that your wife tells you.
她想看你搞你好朋友
that she wants to watch you.
可不是天天都有的事
get a party started with your best friends.
是吧
I mean, am I right?
继续说
Go on.
我考虑了一下 还祈祷了一番
So, I slept on it and I prayed on it,
然后我想到了
and then it came to me.
YOLO
Yolo.
什么
Yolo?
人生只有一次
"You only live once."
别做那个
Don't.
抱歉
Sorry.
所以我打给了戴尔 他说
So, I called Dale, and he said…
当然可以了
H-e-double-hockey-sticks, yeah!
戴尔跟黛比商量了一下
Dale ran it by Deb…
我们本来只打算去吃自助的
We were only gonna get buffet anyway.
所以他们就来了
And here we are.
我没想到我会这么紧张 不过
I didn't think I'd be this nervous, but…
别紧张 我们会很温柔的
Don't worry. We'll be gentle.
- 才不会呢 - 戴尔
- Not! - Oh, Dale!
总之 今天是你的生日
Anyhoo, it's your day, birthday girl.
你说开始 我们就搞起来
You just say go, and, heck… we will light this candle.
玛恩 车没问题吧
Marn? Everything okay with the car?
没事
It's fine.
没事的
Just fine.
（纳克尔斯郡医疗中心）
医生说生产会不太轻松 但詹妮
The doc said it was gonna be a tough birth, but Janie…
她很坚强
…She stepped up.
龙卷风袭来 停电了
The twister hit, the power went out.
她还继续了下去
She just kept on going.
没打麻药
No drugs.
毫不畏缩地把这小东西推出来了
Just pushed out this little dewdrop like she was nothing.
然后詹妮开始流血
Then Janie started bleeding.
他们尽力了
They tried, but…
按理说他们该知道如何止血才对
you'd think they'd know how to stop something like that.
我很抱歉 迈克
I'm so sorry, Mike.
你能跟我们说说这里发生了什么吗
You think you could tell us what happened here?
我之后走了出去
I went outside, after.
想镇定下来
Collect myself.
一车人下来了
A truckload of 'em pulled up.
道路维修工吗
The road crew?
他们什么都没说
They didn't say nothing.
就发疯了
They just went off,
像是着了魔一样到处袭击人
attacking folks like they were possessed.
我冲回去救孩子
I tore back inside to get this little one.
找到了那个储藏室
I found that supply closet,
然后就一直待在里面了
and you know, been there since.
但我能听到他们
I could hear them, though.
到处发狂
Tearing through the halls.
医生 护士 他们根本不管
Doctors, nurses… they didn't care.
你说道路维修工发疯了
You said the road crew went nuts.
他们没来找你麻烦吗
Did any of them come after you?
有几个
Yeah, a few of them.
他们切伤你了吗 或者把血滴在你身上了
Did they cut you or bleed on you?
是的
They did.
我不明白 你什么意思
I don't understand. What are you saying?
不管这是什么
Saying that whatever this is,
可能是会传染的
it might be transmittable.
什么 我们都不知道这是怎么回事
What? We don't even know what this is.
你还说它能传播
Now you're saying it can be passed on?
他说得对
He's right.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
我体内
Inside.
在发生变化
Something's happening.
你受袭到现在多久了
How long has it been since you were attacked?
三四个小时
Three, four hours.
真正的问题是
The real question is,
再过多久我也会变成他们那样
how long till I become like them?
兄弟们 姐妹们
Brothers, sisters…
我知道我没这个权利
I know I have no right,
我没有资格求你们任何事
I have no standing to ask you… you anything,
但情况危急 我必须求你们
but these are desperate times, so ask I must.
我忏悔我的过错
I confess my transgressions,
我愿接受你们的任何惩罚
and I will accept whatever punishment you dole out.
我
Now, I…
求你们帮我
I ask you to help me.
求你们
Please.
别让我做出更可怕的事
Save me from doing worse.
你知道我的立场
Well, you know where I stand.
不 不行
No, you're not…
你们不是认真的吧
You can't be serious.
如果他出去 会被他们杀了的
And if he goes out there, they'll kill him.
那我们就等着他杀我们吗
So, we just wait around for him to kill us?
嗯 这是个好计划
Oh, yeah, that's… that's a plan.
或者我们等着他死掉
Or we just wait for him to die.
之前有个…随你怎么叫
There was a… whatever you want to call it…
疯子 在袭击储藏室门
a "rabid" attacking the closet door,
然后他突然死了
and he just died.
这些东西寿命很短的
These things have a shelf life.
我简直难以置信
I can't believe what I'm hearing here.
不 他说得对
No, he's right.
我们把他关起来 去找解药
We lock him up, we find a cure.
这是间医院
This is a hospital.
算是直觉吧
Yeah, well, call it a hunch,
但我觉得这毛病医书里不会有的
but I don't think you're gonna find this in the medical books.
我打开储藏室的门不是想找解药
I didn't open up that closet door to find a cure.
迈克 很抱歉 但这是不可能的
Look, Mike, I'm sorry, but this is untenable.
我知道
I know.
所以或许我们可以做个交易
That's why I thought maybe we could make a deal.
我去
I'll go.
找个安静的地方 待到一切结束
find somewhere quiet and lay low until this is over.
你救我的女儿
And you save my baby girl.
嗯
Yeah.
说定了
You've got yourself a deal.
多谢你 真的
And I thank you for that. I truly do.
但我不是在跟你说话
But I wasn't talking to you.
我认识你
I know you.
你还是个孩子时 我就在教堂见过你
I've seen you in church since you were knee-high.
求你
Please.
我连豚鼠都没养过
I don't even own a guinea pig.
好了 小姑娘
There you go, little girl.
好了
There you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你们
Thank you all.
我为什么觉得
Why do I get the feeling.
回头我们会好心没好报
that that is gonna bite us in the ass?
没问题吧
You good?
嗯 好极了
Oh, yeah. Aces.
好了 拿上装备
All right, let's gear up.
这可不好办
That might be tricky.
他干什么呢
What's he doing?
- 迪恩 - 我们做出了承诺
- Dean… - We made a promise.
做什么 带着枪冲出去吗
To do what? Charge out there, guns blazing?
我们都不知道怎么杀掉他们
We don't even know how to kill them.
她知道 打胸部 是吧 我猜是心脏
She does. Chest, right? I'm guessing heart.
这太疯狂了
This is madness.
不 那才叫疯狂呢
No. No, that is madness.
这才是正常
This is horse sense.
拯救迈克的孩子 但打死迈克
Save Mike's baby, but shoot Mike.
这怎么正常了
Tell me where that makes sense.
我们可以等着他们死掉
Look, we can just wait for them to die.
那要多久
And how long is that?
如果他们感染了别人又要等多久
And when they infect others, how long is that?
不 我们留在这儿 孩子必死无疑
No, we stay here, that baby dies.
是我们的错 萨姆
We did this, Sam.
好吗
Okay?
我们闯的祸 我们兜着
We broke it, we bought it.
你知道没别的办法
You know there's no other way.
你小子去哪了 小卡
Where the hell are you, Cass?
我没事
I'm…I'm okay.
你听上去不像没事
You don't sound okay.
迪恩 我没事
Dean, I am fine.
而且 你也解决不了我的问题
Besides, what I have, you can't help me.
什么意思
What do you mean, what you have?
告诉萨姆
Just please tell Sam…
罗威娜拿着《诅咒之书》和法典逃跑了
Rowena escaped with The Book of the Damned and the codex.
好吧 别管罗威娜了 你在哪
Okay, forget Rowena. Where are you?
告诉我 血印
Now, you tell me… the mark…
不是吧 发生这么多 你还担心我
Oh, really? You're worried about me after everything…
迪恩 去掉了吗
Dean, is it gone?
是的 我没事了
Yes. I'm good.
我不是很好
I mean, I'm not great.
我也一样
That's two of us.
这是好事
This is good news.
小卡
Hey, Cass.
萨姆
Sam.
好了 该你了 跟我们说说黑暗
Okay, your turn. Talk to us about the darkness.
我为什么要说黑暗的事
Why would I talk about the darkness?
因为它被释放了
Because it's free.
不 不可能
No, that can't be.
移除血印打开了一个锁
Removing the mark opened some kind of lock.
迪恩看到她了
Dean saw her.
黑暗是个女的
The darkness is a woman?
我们问的就是这个啊
Well, that's what we're asking you.
我们还指望你能说说
We were hoping you could tell us.
这是多糟的情况呢
what kind of Defcon screwed we are.
小卡
Cass?
萨姆 迪恩
Sam, Dean…
再见
Goodbye.
我们可能有一阵子不会再见了
It may be some time before we see one another again.
等等 小卡 小卡
Wait, Cass. Cass!
联调局个屁
FBI, my ass.
兄弟们
Brothers.
你们可真够慢的
Took you long enough.
您一召唤我们就尽快赶来了
We came as soon as you called.
该怎么称呼您
What do we call you?
国王啊
King.
那个白人肉身呢
What about the other white meatsuit?
很安全 有另一组人和一个女巫
Secured. We have another team and a witch.
正在移除罗威娜的固定咒语
removing Rowena's immobilization spell as we speak.
有人觉得热吗
Is anybody hot?
我热死了
I'm hot.
应该是更年期的关系 先生
I believe that's the menopause, sir.
谢你提醒
Thank you.
怎么了
What?
没事 先生
Uh, it's nothing, sir.
说
Speak.
只是 您险些被暗杀
It's just, you barely escaped assassination.
您算是正在躲避世上最强大的女巫的追杀
You're arguably on the run from the most powerful witch on earth …
更别说还有个天使了
Not to mention an angel of heaven…
所以呢…
And, uh?
您居然等群交完了才召唤我们帮忙
Y-you didn't call for help until after the orgy?
我道歉…
I apologize…
才怪
for nothing.
听着 我明白 真的
Look, I get it. I do.
我们会救那宝宝的 好吗
We're gonna save that baby, okay?
我们会找到小卡 阻止黑暗
And we're gonna find Cass, and we're gonna stop the darkness.
那还说什么
Okay, so what are we talking about?
我们的计划
The plan.
我们有计划 好吗
We have a plan, okay?
跟以前的计划一样
It's the same plan as it's always been.
要想出去 就得杀出去
In order to get out, we go through.
然后呢
And?
以前的计划都是什么结局
How's that been working for us?
我们困在医院里可救不了小卡 明白吗
We can't save Cass if we're stuck in some hospital, okay?
就像我没法用时光机回到过去
Just like I can't strap on a time machine, go back,
让该隐把血印留着自己玩去
and tell Cain to shove that mark up his ass.
也没法阻止你释放黑暗
or stop you from releasing the darkness.
咱们犯过错吗 当然
Now, have we made mistakes? Yes. Hell, yes.
我们日后可以挨个分析这些错误
And we can analyze each and every one of them.
等我们老掉了牙 喝着冰奶昔
over a couple of frosties when we're old and farting sawdust.
而且不在这间屋子里的时候
and out of this room!
现在 我能做的就是拿着枪冲出去
Right now, all I can do is I can gear up, I can head out,
救下那孩子
and I can save that freaking baby,
我也就要这么做
which is exactly what I'm gonna do.
我们是什么时候忘了该怎么做了
When did we forget how to do this?
怎么了
What?
迪恩 如果我们现在不改变
Dean, if we don't change … right now …
以前的所有破事还会继续重演
All of our crap is just gonna keep repeating itself.
我没听懂 你说什么
Hey, I-I don't even … what?
这种「先下手后考虑」的作风
This … this "kill first, question later."
我们到底怎么了
What happened to us?
除妖猎魔 我们很擅长
Hunting things … we're good at that.
当然 我们甚至很精通
Sure, we're great at that.
但那只是半个标语 伙计
But that's only half of the bumper sticker, man.
萨姆 我是想救那孩子
Sam, I am trying to save that baby.
那外面的其他人呢
And what about the others out there?
你是说那些想杀我们的人吗
You mean the ones trying to kill us?
我是说那些病人 那些垂死的人
I mean the ones that are sick, the ones that are dying.
对 那些不传染我们就不会罢休的人
Yeah, who won't rest until they've infected us all.
那我们就不管找解药了吗
So we just forget about a cure?
什么解药 珍娜的解药吗
What cure? Jenna's cure?
总会有解药的
There is always a cure.
只是我们得决心找到它
You just have to want to find it.
好吧 你要是死了还怎么找
Yeah, how are you gonna find it if you're dead?
咱们又回到原点了
And around and around we go.
救人意味着要救所有人 迪恩
Saving people means all of the people, Dean.
不是只救一个孩子
Not just that baby.
不是只救彼此
Not just each other.
我释放了一股能摧毁一切的力量
I unleashed a force on this world.
到这世上 只为了救你
that could destroy it… To save you.
我告诉你别那么做了
And I told you not to.
重来一次我还是会那么做
And I'd do it again.
毫不犹豫
In a second, I would do it again.
这就是我要说的
And that is what I'm talking about.
这不是你的责任 是咱们俩的
This isn't on you. It is on us.
我们得改变
We have to change.
你有什么想法
What are you thinking?
带珍娜上车
Get Jenna to the car.
带她和孩子去个安全的地方
Get her and the baby somewhere safe.
一枪不发地做到吗
Without a shot.
而且跟着我们的那些东西怎么办
And what are we gonna do about those things on our tail?
他们不会跟着你们了
They won't be on your tail.
不行
No way.
你也说了 迪恩 是我们闯的祸
You said it, Dean. We broke this.
对 是我们闯的祸 我们
Yeah, we broke this, okay? We did.
你答应照顾孩子时
I heard it in your voice.
我从你的声音里听出来了
when you agreed to take that child.
我理解 你做你该做的
I get it. You do what you do.
但你也得让我做我该做的
But you've got to let me do what I do, too.
这边
Over here!
来
Come on.
来抓我啊 你们这些狗娘养的
Come and get me, you sons of bitches!
别这么做 让我帮你们
Don't do this. Let me help you.
来吧
Come on.
孩子
The baby.
不
No.
孩子
The baby.
不行
No.
我们不会伤害你的 迈克
We're not gonna hurt you, Mike.
只要你不碰那孩子
As long as you leave that baby alone.
迈克
Mike.
阿玛拉
Amara.
什么
What?
她的名字
Her name…
是阿玛拉
is Amara.
爸爸回来了
Daddy's home.
怎么了
What?
先生
Sir…
地狱里有流言
There are rumors from hell.
流言
Rumors?
黑暗被释放了
The darkness has been released.
黑暗
The darkness?
拜托 神话 睡前故事而已
Please. Myth. It's a bedtime story.
是恶魔爸爸吓唬小恶魔
Something that daddy demons threaten toddler demons with.
逼他们吃蔬菜的故事
to get them to eat their vegetables.
就算是真的 有什么要紧的
Even if it was true, what's the concern?
黑暗 地狱之王 天生盟友
Darkness, king of hell … natural allies.
只是…发生了点事 先生
It's just … something happened, sir…
笼子里有动静
In the cage.
什么
What?
他们说听起来像是受惊的动物
Uh, they said it sounded like a frightened animal.
整个地狱都听到了 就像是有人发疯了
All of hell heard … like someone was going crazy.
流言说是米迦勒或路西法
The rumor is that Michael or Lucifer …
是他们想要警告我们
one of them is trying to warn us.
警惕黑暗
About the darkness.
荒谬
Ridiculous.
只不过…
Except…
半个地狱的恶魔都吓坏了 先生
Half of hell is sort of freaking out, sir.
我们怎么办
What do we do?
梅塔特隆逃走之后
After Metatron escaped,
我们转移了天堂之门
we moved the door to heaven.
真聪明
Yeah, smart.
为了防止再出事故
You know, to prevent further incidents.
当然 我也会这么做的
Of course. I would have done the same thing.
我们回去前 我们得找个女巫
Before we go back, we need to find a witch.
或是其他懂得法术的人移除…
or someone who knows spellcraft to remove the…
我不明白
I don't understand.
你们不是要带我回天堂
You're not taking me to heaven.
对
No.
不是
We're not.
你能行吗
Oh, you good?
嗯
Yeah.
婴儿 便便 能出什么差错呢
Baby. Poop. What could go wrong?
祝你成功
Godspeed.
我不知道自己在干什么
I have no idea what I'm doing.
嗯
Right.
听着 我知道情况现在看起来很黑暗
Listen, I know things might seem dark right now …
应该说是漆黑
Hell, call it pitch-black.
你可能看不出来
And you may not be able to see it,
但回归的路就在那里
but your way back is right there.
你和她 你们要互相帮助
You and her. You're gonna help each other.
日出云散
Joy comes in the morning.
我祖母组织了一个《圣经》研习小组
My grandma leads a bible study.
就这样吧
Well, let's go with that.
你没事吧
Hey, you good?
嗯 在镇外40英里处
Yeah, about 40 miles outside of town.
目前看来 这里十分荒僻
As far as I can tell, it's isolated to superior.
很不错
Well, that's something.
你呢 你没事吧
How about you? You okay?
你以为会怎样
What'd you expect?
不管怎样我都会找到解药的
Like it or not, I'm gonna find a cure.
我知道你会的
Yeah, I know you are.
现在情况好糟糕啊
Man, things are screwy right now.
我知道我们没有任何答案
I know we don't have any answers,
但至少我们拿下了一局 知道吗
but at least we got one win, you know?
是啊
I hear you.
好了 我要送珍娜去她祖母家
All right, I'm gonna run Jenna up to her grandmother's.
应该只要几小时
Shouldn't be more than a few hours.
然后我们清理那个小镇
Then we clean up that town.
找到黑暗 收拾她
We find the darkness, and we kick her ass.
嗯 很好 迪恩
Yeah, that's great, Dean.
听起来是个好计划
That…sounds like a plan.
如果你真像人说的那样坏
If you're as bad as they say you are,
那你为什么还不伤害我
why haven't you hurt me?
和你永远不会伤害我的理由是一样的
For the same reason that you'll never hurt me.
我们是联系在一起的 迪恩
We're bound, Dean.
我们会永远联系在一起
We'll always be bound.
你帮助过我
You helped me.
我也帮助了你
I helped you.
不管我在哪里 我是谁
No matter where I am, who I am…
我们永远都会帮助彼此
We will always help each other.